<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Des on arkencl</title>
    <link>https://arkencl.dev/de/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Des on arkencl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://arkencl.dev/de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://arkencl.dev/de/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arkencl.dev/de/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, dear Reader!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Georg Göring, a masters graduate in Computer Science.
Programming and by proxy the act of learning always has been a passion of mine as evidenced by a constant involvement in one of, if not the largest
programming discord servers with 40000+ members where I&amp;rsquo;ve been active as a moderator and as a helper primarily in java.
I&amp;rsquo;m also a member of a Java User Group called JUG Ostfalen which is active in the wider area of Brunswick and Wolfsburg.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After acquiring my degree the April of 2020, i&amp;rsquo;ve also started working on numerous side projects and hope to widen my technological horizon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;jug-ostfalen&#34;&gt;JUG Ostfalen&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you somewhere in the wider area of Brunswick and are an interested Java Developer?
Then visit the following link of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jug-ostfalen.de/&#34;&gt;JUG Ostfalen&lt;/a&gt;. A great source
of knowledge in the java ecosystem and a growing community that writes articles, holds regular talks
and organizes workshops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;discord&#34;&gt;Discord&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to join &lt;a href=&#34;discord.gg/programming&#34;&gt;The Programmers Hangout&lt;/a&gt; one of the largest programming discord servers with 40000+ members.
Make sure to familiarize yourself with our rules when joining and I hope you have great time learning and chatting with everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;languages&#34;&gt;Languages&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m proficient in the java ecosystem including the enterprise edition apis and the Spring Framework including Spring Boot and its numerous starters. As well as some light scripting with Groovy primarily in Jenkins Pipelines or Jenkins Pipeline Libraries. Dabbling in different languages as time goes on by creating projects I find personally interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;databases&#34;&gt;Databases&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve professionally worked with PostgreSQL, MySQL, Oracle DB, DB2 LUW/zOS and Neo4j.
In my open source projects so far I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying out mongodb, sqlite, mariadb
and plan to dip into a couple of other Database Systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hobbies&#34;&gt;Hobbies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides Programming and Gaming (Boardgames, Pen&amp;amp;Paper and of course videogames)
on my PC, i also like to drive around with my bicycle or some simple running
to stay healthy and enjoy the nature around me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
